[{
    "theme": "Consumeren (Engels) II ðŸŒ±",
    "langread": "en",
    "questions": [{
            "question": "vegetarian (adj.)",
            "answers": ["vegetarisch"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to realize",
            "answers": ["beseffen"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to protect",
            "answers": ["beschermen"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to produce",
            "answers": ["produceren"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to kill",
            "answers": ["doden"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to slaughter",
            "answers": ["slachten"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to refuse",
            "answers": ["weigeren"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to grow up",
            "answers": ["opgroeien"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to emit",
            "answers": ["uitstoten"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to take care of",
            "answers": ["zorgen voor"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to defend oneself",
            "answers": ["zich verdedigen"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to take care of oneself",
            "answers": ["zich verzorgen"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to suffer",
            "answers": ["lijden"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to die",
            "answers": ["sterven"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to replace",
            "answers": ["vervangen"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to eat up",
            "answers": ["opeten"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to have risk of",
            "answers": ["risico hebben op"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to be right",
            "answers": ["gelijk hebben"]
        },
        {
            "question": "in the end",
            "answers": ["op het einde"]
        },
        {
            "question": "before",
            "answers": ["voordat"]
        },
        {
            "question": "when (past)",
            "answers": ["toen"]
        },
        {
            "question": "during",
            "answers": ["tijdens"]
        },
        {
            "question": "after",
            "answers": ["na"]
        },
        {
            "question": "eventually",
            "answers": ["uiteindelijk"]
        },
        {
            "question": "program makers",
            "answers": ["de programmamakers"]
        },
        {
            "question": "the audience",
            "answers": ["het publiek"]
        },
        {
            "question": "oxygen",
            "answers": ["zuurstof"]
        },
        {
            "question": "female deer",
            "answers": ["de hinde"]
        },
        {
            "question": "pigeon",
            "answers": ["de duif"]
        },
        {
            "question": "lobster",
            "answers": ["de kreeft"]
        },
        {
            "question": "ants",
            "answers": ["de mieren"]
        },
        {
            "question": "grasshoppers",
            "answers": ["de sprinkhanen"]
        },
        {
            "question": "caterpillars",
            "answers": ["de rupsen"]
        },
        {
            "question": "snails",
            "answers": ["de slakken"]
        },
        {
            "question": "deforestation",
            "answers": ["de ontbossing"]
        },
        {
            "question": "crueler",
            "answers": ["wreder"]
        }
    ]
}]